

## MAGGIE ZHANG

#### **Graphic and Interactive Designer**

I am a Candidate for Bachelor of Arts in Design + Interaction at Northeastern University. As a second year, I have experience with design software and processes both in and out of the classroom. I'm always excited to contribute and learn more!

E-mail zhang.ma@husky.neu.edu

#### Age 20

Language English (Native)

Chinese (Limited)

Objective Gain experience in a

working environment.

#### **SKILLS & EXPERTISE**

Photoshop

Illustrator

InDesign

Premiere Pro

After Effects

HTML + CSS

Photography ••••• OO Illustration

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### Northeastern Chinese Student Association

Media Specialist | May 2015 - Present

Created promotional content for major events, including posters and videos. Also photographed members and organize activities.

#### Society of Asian Scientists and Engineers

Advertising Committee | Sept 2015 - Feb 2016

Designed advertisements, name badges, and tote bags for the 2016 SASE Northeast Regional Conference. Created a 16 page program of events for guests.

#### East Coast Asian Student Union

Marketing/Outreach Committee | Oct 2014 - Feb 2015

Assisted in organizing a conference about AAPI identities. Worked with team to establish a visual identity and design conference posters and letterheads.

### **EDUCATION**

#### Northeastern University

BFA Interaction Design | 2014 - Present

Coursework includes Typography, Design Process Context and Systems, and art and design history (ancient to contemporary); as well as basic programing, animation, and film. GPA: 3.8.

# Rhode Island School of Design - Continuing Education Branding and Website | Summer 2014, 2015

Completed workshops in Identity Design + Branding and Web Design. Finished with a 14 page identity manual and three independently-coded, responsive websites.

## PERSONAL HOBBIES

Classical Chinese dance Hip-Hip / Modern Dance Oil Painting and Sketching